Guide to the William R. Rambo Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
William R. Rambo papers
1939-1992
1954-1974
SC0132
Rambo, William R. (William Ralph), 1916-
35 Linear feet (29 boxes)
These papers, kept in their original arrangement, reflect Prof. Rambo's administrative responsibilities as well as his research interests, largely during his time at Stanford University. Stanford subjects include the School of Engineering, the Electrical Engineering Department, the Stanford Electronic Labs, the Applied Electronics Lab, research policy at Stanford, courses, the Academic Senate, the University Land and Building Development Committee, and student demonstrations. Other subjects include the American Society for Engineering Education, Engineering College Research Council, Joint Services Electronic Program, and Rambo's research work with the U.S. Army, Air Force, and Navy.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Gift of William R. Rambo, 1975, 1976, 1997.
Information about Access
This collection is open for research.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
William R. Rambo was born September 3, 1916. He received his B.A. and Electrical Engineering degrees from Stanford University in 1938 and 1941. He was a research associate at the Harvard Radio Research Lab and a research engineer with Airborne Instruments Lab in New York before coming to Stanford as a research associate in 1951. He was made a Professor of Electrical Engineering in 1957, Director of Electronics Labs in 1960, and Associate Dean of the School of Engineering in 1961. He retired as a Professor Emeritus in 1972.
Description of the Collection
These papers, kept in their original arrangement, reflect Prof. Rambo's administrative responsibilities as well as his research interests, largely during his time at Stanford University. Stanford subjects include the School of Engineering, the Electrical Engineering Department, the Stanford Electronic Labs, the Applied Electronics Lab, research policy at Stanford, courses, the Academic Senate, the University Land and Building Development Committee, and student demonstrations. Other subjects include the American Society for Engineering Education, Engineering College Research Council, Joint Services Electronic Program, and Rambo's research work with the U.S. Army, Air Force, and Navy.
The first twenty boxes were given to the Stanford University Archives by Prof. Rambo in 1975 and 1976. In 1997, he gave an additional nine boxes of materials containing his chron files for 1961-72 and subject files and a photo album on student umest at Stanford, 1966-73. Dr. Rambo's descriptive inventory for the student unrest files is included with the box and folder listing.
Scope and Contents
Common abbreviations used in this collection
AEL - Applied Electronics Lab ARPA - Advanced Research Projects Agency ASEE - American Society for Engineering Education ASSU - Associated Students of Stanford University DoD - Department of Defense DSL - Digital Systems Lab DUR - Durand Bldg. ERL - Electronics Research Lab IEEE - Institute of Electrical & Electronic Engineers, Inc. IPR - Institute for Plasma Research ISL - Information Systems Lab JSEP - Joint Services Electronics Program McC - McCullough Bldg. NASA - National Aeronautics and Space Administration N.I.G.M.S. - National Institute of General Medical Sciences NSF - National Science Foundation SEL - Stanford Electronics Laboratories SES - Student Education Council SLAC - Stanford Linear Accelerator Center SRI - Stanford Research Institute STL - Systems Techniques Lab TAC - Technical Advisory Committee (Joint Services Electronics Program)
Arrangement note
The collection consits of one series and one addition: 1. Papers, 1939-1975.
Access Terms
Rambo, William R. (William Ralph), 1916-; Stanford Electronics Laboratories.; Stanford University. Academic Council.; Stanford University. Applied Electronics Laboratory.; Stanford University. Department of Electrical Engineering. Faculty.; Stanford University. Faculty Senate.; Stanford University. School of Engineering.; Stanford University. Stanford Electronics Laboratories.; Engineering research.; Student movements.
Collection Contents
- Original Accession, 1939-1975
  The series is arranged in twenty three subseries: 1. Electrical Engineering Department, 1966-1971. 2. School of Engineering, undated. 3. Space Engineering Building, 1964-1968. 4. Field sites, 1961-1968. 5. Buildings, 1960-1968. 6. University, 1963-1970. 7. Student records, 1964-1971. 8. Courses, 1962-1968. 9. Personnel, undated. 10. Correspondence - foreign, undated. 11. Electrical Engineering Department, 1964-1966. 12. Academic Council, undated. 13. School of Engineering, 1964-1972. 14. University, 1950-1975. 15. ASEE [American Society for Engineering Education], 1964-1971. 16. Telecommunication Science Panel, 1966. 17. Teaching Library, 1955-1969. 18. University, personal & miscellaneous material, 1953-1971. 19. JSEP [Joint Services Electronics Program], 1963-1972. 20. University, 1961-1972. 21. School of Engineering: Stanford Electronic Labs; consulting and research, 1949-1973. 22. Speeches and articles (arr. chronologically), 1945-1974. 23. Personal and miscellaneous material, 1939-1974.
  - Electrical Engineering Department, 1966-1971
    See also boxes 5 and 13.
    - Pantell Committee Report, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Annual Report to the President, Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Executive Comm. Minutes, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Bell Telephone, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Stores Committee, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Dept. EE Exec. Committee, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Dept. EE Exec. Committee - McC 240, 1970 Oct 21 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Dept. EE Exec. Committee, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Executive Committee, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Faculty meetings, Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Faculty, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Executive Comm. Minutes, 1967-1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Ph.D candidates, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Post masters admission corrsp., Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Procedures re PhD program, etc., Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Dave Bacon, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Barry, George H., Undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Appointment - Dr. Alfred Braun, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - School of Engineering, Undated
    Individual files are undated.
    - Buneman, Oscar (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Cox, Donald (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Cover, Thomas (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Cumming, Raymond C. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Crawford, Frederick W. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Debra, Daniel B. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Dunn, Donald A. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - daRosa, Alda (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Derfler, Heinrich (Pending) (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Goodman, Joseph (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Grace, Donald J. (Assoc. Dean) (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Howard, H. Taylor (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Kailath, Thomas (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - Kincheloe, Wm. Robert, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - Kino, Gordon Stanley (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - Luenberger, David (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - May, Bill B. (Dr.) (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - Moll, John (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - Biographies (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - Faculty appt. forms ( pgs. 1-9) (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - Self, Dr. Sidney (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - Spicer, Wm. E. (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - Smallwood, Richard (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - Terman, F.T. (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Waterman, A.T., Jr. (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Weaver, Charles S. (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Villard, Oswald G., Jr. (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Space Engineering Building, 1964-1968
    - Proposal to NASA, Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Use Agreement, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Corrsp., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Corrsp., 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Building 530/540 corrsp., 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Field sites, 1961-1968
    - Correspondence, 1964-1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Printed matter/maps, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Field site/freeway/problems, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Parking/storage/antennas, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Buildings, 1960-1968
    - Building correspondence, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Design Engineering Bldg., corresp., Undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - New buildings - requirements, Undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Engineering Bldg. - miscell., Undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Engineering Library study, Undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Engineering Bldg., 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Chemical Engineering Bldg., Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - McCullough Bldg. - furnishings, Undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - McCullough Bldg. - fume hoods, Undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - McCullough Bldg. - Policy Comm., Undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - McCullough - misc., 1964-1966 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - McCullough Bldg. - space assignments, Undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - McCullough Engineering Bldg., 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - McCullough - dedication, Undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - McCullough - Microwave Lab move, Undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Architectural Selection Comm. corrsp., Undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Theater (#128b), Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Music Bldg. (#128c ), Undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Central Food Service (#383c) - Program, 1968 Sep 16 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Athletics Master Plan - revision (#205c), Undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Main Library development (458 ), Undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - GT&E [General Telephone and Electronics] activation - miscellaneous, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - GT&E space requests, Undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - STL [Systems Techniques Lab] - space reassignments, 1964-1965 (Box 34)
    - Systems Theory, Undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - EE [Electrical Engineering] - labs and offices, Undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - AEL-ERL [Applied Electronics Lab, Electronics Research Lab]- general maps, space assignments, etc., Undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - AEL first floor renovation, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Computer Science Bldg. (#531), Undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Meyer Memorial Basement (#539), Undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Chemistry new facilities (#509), Undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Aerospace Engineering-Air Force -- Johns Hopkins Building, Undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Aerospace Engineering-Air Force -- Denver Research Institute, Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Aerospace Engineering-NASA -- miscell. data, Undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Aerospace Engineering-NASA -- general, Undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Aerospace Engineering-NASA -- additional data proposal SE 2-64, Undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Aerospace Engineering-Air Force -- additional data proposal SE 1-65 (letter to Angelos), 1965 Nov 4 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Aerospace Engineering-Air Force -- general, Undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Aerospace Engineering - corporate: University proposals to private and corporate donors, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Aerospace Engineering: "A New Building for Space Engineering and Science at Stanford University", Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Aerospace Engineering - NASA: Memorandum of Understanding, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - NASA Building - Radioscience (Villard), Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - NASA Building - Aero & Astro (Bershader), Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - NASA Building - Guidance & Control (Cannon), Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - NASA Building - "Working Papers" (for Holmes Visit), 1964 Oct 31 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Aerospace Engineering: University discussions (includes Board of Trustees actions), Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Aerospace Engineering - NASA: facilities grant brochures, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - NASA Building - Laboratory for Mathematical... (suppes), Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Air Force - Proposal SE 1-65, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Controversy with U.S. Gov. re space assignments in Durand Bldg., Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - University, 1963-1970
    See also boxes 13 and 14.
    - Faculty Research Committee, Schawlow Report, 1970 May 27 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Comm. on Research Dean's Conference Rm. Med .Sch., 1970 Nov 2 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - University Libraries, Unknown (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Miller Research Fellowships, Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Patent policy correspondence, Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Hare Voting System, Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Selective Service info., 1968 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Don Hornig/Lyman/ Funding, 1968 Feb (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Committee on University Policy, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Misc. research funding, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Annual financial report/corresp., Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Computer Planning-Pres. Comm., 1965 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Contract corresp., Undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Indirect cost rates/cost shar., Undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Policy re budgets, etc., Undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Interdisciplinary research, Undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Study of education - Packer, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - University research funding, Undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Research support/unrestricted funds (by Labs ), Undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - University Salary Policy Comm., Undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Endowed Lectures Series, Undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Summer employment, Undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Publications (AEL) [Applied Electronics Lab], Undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Secr. charges to EE, Undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - SEL [Stanford Electronics Laboratories] expenditures/ by Laboratory), Undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Youth Opportunity Program, Undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - ABM [Anti-Ballistic Missile Safeguard System), Undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Research Information Center Report, Undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Undergraduate Engineering Council, Undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Academic Council/Comm. of 15, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Academic Council (Exec. Comm.), 1966 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Minority Group Questionaire - R. W. Lyman, Undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Slomich, Jet Propulsion Lab, 1967 Dec-1968 Mar (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Franklin Committee, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Advisory Comm. - campus disruption, Undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Sit-in Petition, Undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Miscellaneous disruptions, Undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Research problems, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Miscell., including DOD relationships, funding security review, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Discussion of overhead, 1970 Oct 20 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Staff letter, Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Committee of Fifteen, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Interim Judicial Body - misc. file, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - I.J.B. - 1967, C.I.A. - 1968, 1967, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Marc Sapir, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Couzens and Ackerley case, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Interim Judicial Board - Harris case, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Case of Alan Traister, Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Stanford Electronics Laboratories, 1964-1971
      - Personnel-staff & faculty miscell., A-L, Undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - Personnel-staff & faculty miscell., M-Z, Undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - Laboratory reorganization, Undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - Tube Lab, Undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - Standard Computer - McCluskey, Undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - Activities Committee, Undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - Machine Shop Committee, Undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - History of SEL, Undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - Computer Committee, Undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - Editorial/Publications Comm., Undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Motion picture/Matt Lehmann, Undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
      - Holography, Undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
      - Research assistantships, 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 40)
      - ERL [Electronics Research Laboratory] space discussions, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - ERL, AEL [Applied Electronics Lab], DUR [Durand Bldg.] - space allocation, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Monthly lab expenditure reports, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Memo to Research Steering Committee (subcontracting ), Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - N.I.G.M.S. [National Institute of General Medical Sciences], Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
      - Staff benefits/Scroggs/SU, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 6)
      - Information Systems Lab, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
      - Digital Systems Lab, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
      - STL [Systems Techniques Lab] - misc. correspondence & notes, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
      - STL - EE 193/293 participation, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - STL - Committee meetings, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 11)
      - STL - income/expense projection file, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 12)
      - STL - spectrum allocation, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 13)
      - STL - Laser correspondence - misc., Undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
      - STL - Instrument Committee, Undated (Box 6, Folder 15)
      - Research Steering Committee (SEL), Undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
      - STL - electronic instrumentation, Undated (Box 6, Folder 17)
      - STL - fast Fourier transforms, Undated (Box 6, Folder 18)
      - STL - RADA system review file, Undated (Box 6, Folder 19)
      - STL - telecommunications, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 20)
      - STL - story (Don Grace), 1965 (Box 6, Folder 21)
        Slides.
      - Radioscience Lab - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 6, Folder 22)
      - Radioscience Lab - West ARRA, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 23)
      - Radioscience Lab - Bracewell AF-53/Radio Astronomy, Undated (Box 6, Folder 24)
      - Radioscience Lab - Center for Radar Astronomy (64), Undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
      - Plasma Physics - correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 26)
      - Aero & Astro - misc. correspondence, Undated (Box 6, Folder 27)
      - Plasma Physics - misc. correspondence, 1967-1971 (Box 6, Folder 28)
      - Systems Theory - correspondence, misc., Undated (Box 6, Folder 29)
      - Systems Theory - Kailath - re industrial affils., Undated (Box 6, Folder 30)
      - Solid State - correspondence, misc., Undated (Box 6, Folder 31)
      - Electronics research at Stanford, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 32)
      - SRI (and AAUP Colloq.), 1969 Feb (Box 6, Folder 33)
      - Research Policy Committee & patent policy, Undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
      - DoD security review, Undated (Box 6, Folder 35)
      - "Engineer in Society" and res. strike, 1969 Mar 4 (Box 6, Folder 36)
      - Ad Hoc Faculty Information Comm., Undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
      - Discussions of research, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 38)
      - Research discussions, Undated (Box 6, Folder 39)
      - Land & building dev. notes, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Student records, 1964-1971
    - Jones, Sid (survey), Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - I-X, Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - C, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Robert W. Burton, Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - L-M, Undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - H, Undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - D-G, Undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - N-R, Undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - S, Undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - T-Z, Undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Advisees, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Pre-registration, Undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - L.P. Brooks, Undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Advising lists and present advisees, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - A-B, Undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Matthews, A.R., Personnel, Undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Advisee comments for Pritchard, Undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Advisees, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Advisees, 1964-1969 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Eckhard Schulz, Undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - I.J.B. ASSU Judicial Council, Undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Courses, 1962-1968
    - EE [Electrical Engineering] 180a, Undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - EE 179, Undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - EE 162 - general, miscellaneous, Undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - EE 162 - homework solutions, Undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - EE 162 - examinations, Undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - EE - Undergraduate Administration, 150, 160 series discussions, Undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Long-Range Planning, programmed instruction, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Long-Range Planning, undergraduate curriculum flexibility, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - EE 161 - Ray Cumming class notes, 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - EE 161 - examinations, Undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - EE 161: HF equivalent circuits of vacuum tubes & transistors, Undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - EE 160 - general, "Class Notes on Electronic Circuits", Cumming, Undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - EE 161 - general, Undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - EE 161- homework, Undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Engr. 199/299, Undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - EE 213H - class note 1, Undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - EE 180a, 180b, Undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Engr. 199, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Engr. 199, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - EE 159 - Fall (New Ideas), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - EE 240, Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Engr. 199, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - EE 180, Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - EE 180a, 1966, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - EE 180a - class notes on modulation systems, Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - EE 180b, 1963, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - General course information, Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Personnel, Undated
    Files are undated.
    - A-C (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - General (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - S (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - D-G (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - H-K (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - L-M (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - T-Z (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - N-R (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence - foreign, Undated
    - UK - miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Foreign - miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - UK - British Embassy (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Canada (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Electrical Engineering Department, 1964-1966
    - Divisional origin EE(JGL), 1964 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - SEES Seminar - student position papers, Undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Tony Siegman MS program corrsp., Undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Corrsp. Master of Science Degree, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Academic Council, Undated
    Most files are undated. Exceptions are noted in the file listing.
    - Steering Comm. #900-949 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Steering Comm. - miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Steering Comm. - #950-999 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Steering Comm. - #850-899 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Steering Comm. - #800-849 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Steering Comm. - #749-799 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Steering Comm. - #691-749 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Advisory Board (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Advisory Board, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Advisory Board, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Academic Senate - correspondence & printed matter (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Academic Senate - #700-749 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Academic Senate - #650-699 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Academic Senate - #601-649 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Academic Senate - #550-599 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Academic Senate - #500-549 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Academic Senate - #450-499 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Academic Senate - #400-449 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Academic Senate - #350-399 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Academic Senate - #300-349 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Academic Senate - #250-299 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Academic Senate - #200-249 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Academic Senate - #150-199 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Academic Senate - #100-149 (Box 8, Folder 2)